UNITE Boston Joint Board Records 6000/056
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Boston Joint Board Records
1971-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union (ACTWU)
6000/056
14 cubic feet
14 linear ft.
Records.
7544702
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
D Cohen, February 17, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000 PUBS: UNITE Publications 6000/044 P: UNITE Photographs 6000/056 AV: UNITE Boston Joint Board Audio-Visual Materials
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Boston Joint Board; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Boston Joint Board; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7544702
- Activity Reports. (Box 1)
  - Activity Reports - Cummings 96, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Activity Reports - G. Decray 96, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Activity Reports - A. DaCosta 96, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Activity Reports - J. Devine 96, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Activity Reports - J. Paun 96, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Activity Report L. Palmer 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Activity Reports - C. Maheu 96, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Local 1560T Contracts/ Membership Lists, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Local - 1560T 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local 1569T Contracts/Membership Lists, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Local - 1569J 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local 1712T Contracts/Membership Lists, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Contract 1723T, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Local - 1723T 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 2527T Contracts, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Local - 2527T 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Local 2687T Contracts/ Membership Lists, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Local - 1712T 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Local - 2687T 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Arbitration Dates 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Local 311 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Local 313 2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Liz Claiborne Local 324, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Local 377 2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Riverside Manufacturing Local 377, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Biddeford Blankets Local 1856, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Marshalls Local 1999, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Local 2001 2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Local 2624 2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Fibre Leather Manufacturing Local 88, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Futuramik Local 151, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bradley Scott Co Local 177, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - National Envelope Local 2654, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Local 3lT Contracts/ Membership Lists, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Local - 110A-T 2003 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Staff Connecticut State AFL-CIO, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Local 110A-T Contracts/Membership Lists, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Local 121H Contracts/Membership Lists, 1971-2002 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Local - 121H 2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Local 471T Contracts/Membership Lists, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Local - 471T 2003 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Local - 477T 2003 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Current Contract 652T, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Mostly arbitration decisions. (Box 2)
  - Swan Finis arb. 2/11/04 Co. Ded. Unauth. Money emp. Pay Reduction of ins. Ben. Antonio Medieros, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration Requests Swan Finishing Local 1483T, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - General Cable - Local 1156T Grievances/Arbitrations, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bill Dazy's Grievances, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Justin/Santoro Arb. Opinion & Award 6/3/99 - Prof. Horowitz, Arbit., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Settled Arbitration 12/16/98 Maria Borba-Dyecraftsmen, Len, Schnei, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Cape Cod & UNITE (Plant Closing) Morris Horowitz Arb. 10/14/98, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Seniority, Caetano, Pereira & Soares Arb. S. Henderson 6/18/97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cliftex Corp. - Attendance Bonus Sharon Henderson - 1/28/1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cliftex Bonus Grievance, Dec. 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cape Cod Vac. Pay Settlement- 5/11/99 Prof. Horoqitz Arbitrator, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Lynn Libby Discharge - Van Baalen 9/23/96 - Ellen Buzbee Arbitrator, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Jennifer Araujo - Lay off 5/20/96 Swiss Art - Arb. Gary D. Altman, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - George Safioleas - Arb. 2/15/96 No. Dartmouth, Office - Swiss-Art, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Arb. Award - Local 1, Sterlingwear Pf. Horowitz Arb. Bonus Payment, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Perley Hodgkin Discharge - 12/21/95 Local 406, Saco. Arb. Philip Dunn, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - January '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - February '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - March '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - April '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - May '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - June '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - July '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - August '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - September '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - October '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - November '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - December '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 1st Quarter Taxes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 2nd Quarter Taxes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 3rd Quarter Taxes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 4th Quarter Taxes, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - End of the Year Taxes (1997) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 1991 Fed/State/FICA/Medicare Books (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Brand Rex, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Union Rates, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Employee Seniority, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Amerbelle, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Ensign - Bickford, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - CSFT CBA '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Staff Union of Connecticut, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - University Health Professionals, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Kenyon Industries (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Ashworth Card Clothing, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Conneticosh, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - General Cable, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Wardwell Braiding Machine Co., 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Cranston Print Works, 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Freudenberg - NOIC, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Mostly contracts. (Box 3)
  - Local - 1362T 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dorr Contract, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Local - 1371T 2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Local 1460T Contract/Membership Lists, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Local 1016T Contracts/ Membership Lists, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Local - 1016T 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Local 1036T Contract/Membership Lists, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Local - 1036T 2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - UNITE Local 1362T Organizing, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Ltrs to Freuchenberg 1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Local 1362T, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Local - 1460T 2003 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - UNITE! Laundry Bargaining Information, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Resources for UNITE! Union Reps (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Memorandums, 1994-1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Robby Len Apparel America, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Robby Len, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Calvin Klein + Rio Papers, 1991-1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Contract Term Info to New England Jt. Bd., 2002 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Contract Termination Letters 2002 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Contract Termination 2003 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - The Garment Industry Development Corporation, Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - The Garment Industry Development Corporation, Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - MacDermid Graphic Arts & Local 841T Grievance Negotiations/Settlements 9/5/2k1, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - W.P.S. Contract Dispute 2001 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Westpoint Stevens Inc., 2003 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Attention Members Local 305T, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Westpoint Stevens Inc. 2003 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - W.P Steven David Cutler, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - West Point Stevens Notification of Termination 1998 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Contract 1998 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Mates W.P.S. 1998 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - CC Union, Human Resources (WPS), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Pension at W. P. Stevens, 1992-1999 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - West Point Stevens Seniority List 1998 April 1 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Westpoint Stevens, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Guy Neveux, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - 305T Contract 1998 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Addresses and Seniority list of W.P. Stevens, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Letter as to Greenville Ala:, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Westpoint Stevens, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - WestPoint Stevens, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Mostly material about the Garment Industry. (Box 4)
  - Dave Goldberg 2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Gordon Garment Training 1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - International Women's Apparel 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Isaac Hazan 2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sequins 1999 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Milady Bridals 1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Montes de OCA 1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - UNITE! Funds, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - GIDC Mgmt. Workshop '92, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NYFI 2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 1999 GIDC (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 1998 GIDC (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - GIDC 1997/1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - GIDC Reports - '98, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - GIDC Grant Proposal '97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - GIDC/Weintrab Quality Prog. '93, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - GIDC Quality Program '92, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - GIDC Profile (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - GIDC Job 1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - New Jersey Job Training 2000 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NU Fashions (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Ronald Karpman, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - NU Fashions '98, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Goddess Move, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Engineering Management, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Mayflower/ Triple A, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Eng. Dep't Expenses, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - GIDC - TC2/ Sloan Grant 2000 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - GIDC 2000/2001 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - GIDC Structure (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - GIDC Budget 2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - GIDC 2001 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - GIDC Board of Directors Meeting, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - GIDC Budget, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - GIDC Board of Directors Meeting, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - PA LMC 2001 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Pennsylania LMC - 2000 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - GIDC/TC2/Sloan Short-Cycle Mfg. Project, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - MINY 1999 /GIDC (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - LA Del 1999/2000 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - CAF/Karpman - Vouchers Invoice, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Gina Coat Fashions - Karpman, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Indigo Jeans/Karpman, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Gloria Gay Coat/Karpman 98/99, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Garment Industry Reports, 1983-1997 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Fashion Industry Booklets, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - "Find a Dorctor or Specialist", 2002 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Ronald Alman, 1991-1997 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Financial records and dues. (Box 5)
  - Agnelo Da Costa, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Richard MacFadyen, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Greater Northeastern Board, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Richard MacFayden, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Random Folders, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Greater Northeastern Joint Board, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Al DaCosta, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - ACTWU, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Greater Northeastern Jt. Board, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Jerry Paun, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Greater Northeastern Jt. Bd., 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Grieco L187 2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Fall River Shirt 2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Miltons 2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Polymers L2624 2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Dyecraftsment ,L2370 2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Dues. (Box 6)
  - American Friends Ser. Local 661 2000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Dues (Kathy Casavant&Mareen Marfione) Local 177, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Bradley Scott 2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Marv Check-Offs- Local 187, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - American London-Norwood, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Tartan Textile Services Local 667 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Filene's 2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - State Coat Front Dues #93, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Swiss-Art, L616TB 2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Sterlinwear, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Aramark Uniforms Local66L 2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Van Baalen L371 2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Stylevek, L2599 2000 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mechanics Uniforms Ser. Local 66L Rental Uniforms Lt, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Morgan Linen, Local 66L, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Rental Uniforms of Ct. Inc, 66L (1 Person), 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Morgan Services, Inc Local 66L Boston 2000/2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Unitech Services Group Inc., 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Unifist Corp. L66L (Pawtucket), 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Whyte's Laundry & Cleaners, Local 66L, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - River Falls Manufacturing 2000 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CIAC 2000 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - UWVR Training, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - MAREIC - Penn State Curriculum, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - E.I. Advice, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Eng. Dep't Personal Notes, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Engineering 1996-8, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Quartet Fashions, 1990-1998 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Bruce Herman, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Industry Development Role, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Brooks Bro., 2001 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - NYC Procurement Issues, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Liz/Limited Sourcing 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Newark Procurement Ordinance, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - NY Uniform Maker Coalition, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - NYC Procurement Campaign, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Vallone on Procurement, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Spano Bill, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - UNITE Procurement Documents, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - UNITE!, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Uniform Lists - Postal, Fire etc., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - University Procurement (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Sweatfree Schools, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Dues. (Box 7)
  - W.P.S. Piece Rate Aveg. 2003 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Westpoint Stevens, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Westpoint Stevens Insurance, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Piece Rate Averages W.P.S. 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Piece Rate Averages 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Insurance W.P.S., 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Robyn Clegg W.P.S., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Piece Rate W. Point Stevens 1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1999 Seniority W.P.P. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Westpoint Stevens Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Union Dues Report 1999 Folder 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Union Dues Report 1999 Folder 2 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Union Dues Report 1999 Folder 3 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Union Dues Report 1999 Folder 4 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Payroll Union Deductions, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Monthly Union Dues Report, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Polyfibron Technologies, Inc., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - ADP Autopay Management Report, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Union Dues Deducted, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Union Dues Deducted, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Codex Book Co. Union Dues 1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Amerbelle Corporation Union Report, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Putnam Precision Molding, Inc., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Deduction History Report (The Harodite Finishing Company), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Autopay Management Report, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Beacon Wiper Corp. Union Dues, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Entex Inc. Union Due, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Korber Hats Inc. Dues, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Weekly Greater Northeastern Joint Board, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - CT Federation of Educational & Professional Employees Dues, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Clark Cutler McDermott Co. Union Dues, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Homestead Industries, Inc Monthly Union Dues for January, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Dues Check Off. (Box 8)
  - Justin Clothing 1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Cape Cod Spts. 1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Cliftex Clothing 1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dartmouth Clo. 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Town & Country Slacks 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Riverside Mfg. 1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - (the new) Anderson Little Local 1069 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Asher Pants Local 309 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Bates Local 121 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Bixby Local 0012A 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Wanaco/Hathaway Local 486 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Whiting, EB&AC Local 438 1996 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Anderson Little Local 1069 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Asher Pants Local 309 1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Cliftex Clothing Local 377 1996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Justin Clothing Local 377 1996 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Town & Country Slacks Local 377 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Check Off. (Box 9)
  - Country Narrow, 1991-2002 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cranston Print, 1991-2002 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Dork Woolen, 1993-2002 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Duro Finishing [Folder 1 of 3], 1991-2002 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Duro Finishing [Folder 2 of 3], 1988-1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Duro Finishing [Folder 3 of 3], 1989-1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Duro 2, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Duro Textile [Folder 1 of 2], 1988-2000 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Duro Textile [Folder 2 of 2], 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Ensign Bickford, 1998-2002 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Fraudenberg [Folder 1 of 3], 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Freudenberg [Folder 2 of 3], 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Freudenberg [Folder 3 of 3], 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Harodits, 1991-2002 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - James River, 1992-2000 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Kenyon [1 of 2], 1996-2001 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Kenyon [Folder 2 of 2], 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Korber Hats, 1991-2003 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Lynn Plastics, 1991-2002 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Microfibres, 2000-2003 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Moldex, 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Putnam Precision Molding, 1995-2002 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Slater Dye [Folder 1 of 2], 1995-2002 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Slater Dye [Folder 2 of 2], 1991-1995 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Swan Finishing, 1991-2002 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Troy Mills, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - U.S. Button, 2000-2003 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Check Off and Receipts. (Box 10)
  - Union Wedding, 1991-2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Vernon Plastics, 1991-2003 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Wardwell Basic, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Receipt - AAA 1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Per Capita Tax Statements UNITE!, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Receipts - AFL-CIO, CLC 1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Receipts - Conn AFL-CIO 1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Receipts - AT&T 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Receipts - American Express 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Receipts - American Express 1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Receipts - Barker Spec. 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Receipts - Building 1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Receipts - BC/BS 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Receipts - Center Capital 1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Receipts - Cellularone 1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - East Coast Building Maint. 1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Receipts - Electic 1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Receipts - Employees Dues 1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Receipts - Express Mail 1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Receipts - Grievances 1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Vendor Files. (Box 11)
  - Ads, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Adler, Steve Computer Consultant 1999 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - American Express 1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Arbitraton, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - AT&T 1999 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Attorney's Fees 1999 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bell Atlantic, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Bell Atlantic Act# 508 673-2964 393 006 4, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Bell Atlantic Act# 617 426-8123 113 008 9, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Bell Atlantic Act# 978 686-2830 831 007 5, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Bell Atlantic Act# 207 284-4611 236 003 6, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bell Atlantic Act# 978 686-7392 113 007 1, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Bell Atlantic Act# 603 625-6929 428 004 5, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Bell Atlantic Act# 617 524-4575 165 008 4, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Bell Atlantic Mobile 1999 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Bell Atlantic Mobil Mike & Martie, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Biddeford Office Expenses 1999 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Building Corporation Expenses paid by the NERJB 1999 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Books and Publications 1999 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - CPA's Orefice & Calari 1999 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Celluar ONE 1999 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Citizen's Credit Union 1999 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 401K Plan NERJB 1999 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Pension Plan Joint Board 1999 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Contributions 1999 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Convention - UNITE '99, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Convention Expenses 1999 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Dental Bills 1999 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Dues Refunds 1999 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Dues/Memberships 1999 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Education Expenses 1999 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Equal NET 1999 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Equipment Purchases 1999 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Fruits & Flowers 1999 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Greater New England Regional Joint Board, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Hampton Inn Westport, MA 1999 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Hampton Inn North Andover, MA, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Insurance 1999 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Investment Fees 1999 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Investment Fees 1998 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Joint Board Meeting Fall 1999 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Joint Board Meeting Spring 1999 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Jt. Bd. Meeting Spring 2000 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - K&R Coffee 1999 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Leary Press 1999 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - New England Regional Joint Board UNITE!, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Leadership School 1999 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Life Insurance 1999 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Local 66L Laundry Office Expenses, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Lost Time 1999 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Lucent Technologies 1999 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Media ONE 1999 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Memberships 1999 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Meetings & Conferences 1999 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Metrocall (Pagers), 1999 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Miscellaneous 1999 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Mobilization Expenses 1999 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Correspondence (Box 12)
  - A and A Negotiations, 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Angela Sport, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Alicare- Correspondence, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Scope and Contents
    5/10/01
  - Apollo Tanning Co., 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Apparel America (Robby Len), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Baron Abramson, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Baron Peters, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Biddeford Textiles, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Bradley Scott, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Brooks Brothers, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Brooks Bros. Contract- Local 340, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    New York Stores
  - Chadwilr's of Boston, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Charlestown Manufacturing, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut Peace Action, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Dyecraftsmen- Contract Negotiations 9/97, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Electro-Flex, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Fall River Shirt Contract Negotiation Notes, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Blue Cross Blue Shield of MA, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Fall River Shirt
  - Fall River Shirts, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 19)